Cause
They say there are bananas.
Bananas are hot.
I usually eat bananas.
This is bad.
I'm so surprised.
I don't know what to say.
Everything I saw was so amazing.
I've seen the stage.
I was so excited to think that I'm going to be standing there today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Rehearsal is going to be a little more important
I'll do my best.
Maybe it's corn soup.
Egg soup?
Delicious.
I'm not sure which one it is.
Egg soup or corn soup?
Here we are. It's the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall.
Well, I just went to see the stage to see what it was like,
Well, it's huge.
It's so big that even the people sitting in the back can enjoy the show,
I hope to make it an enjoyable space so that even the people in the back can have a good time.
We are going to rehearse now, so I will do my best.
Thank you very much.
You feel like a boss?
Yes, I am.
Yes.
It's a good case... bananas.
baritobo country
Yudhoyono, Indonesia
Wow! Thank you very much.
I love Indonesia, don't you?
I love Indonesia.
Okay, I'll go this way.
There's a reason why I love Indonesia.
A game that Kosaku and I often play
Indonesia is very popular.
You've been playing it for a long time?
I've been playing for about three years.
I'm stronger than you.
No, I'm stronger.
I'm definitely stronger than you.
Let's not talk about it.
If we talk about it, we'll get into a fight.
I'm ranked higher than you.
For now.
I'll be fine.
Looks good.
Which one's this?
What should I do with it?
Heisen's place.
Oh, that's good.
Where should we go?
Let's go this way.
Most of the rice is this way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're making less?
Oh, is this the chicken?
Oh, yes. This is what we have here.
Is it seasoned though?
This is the sauce.
I see.
You can pour this over it.
The sauce is onion and ginger sauce.
It's a little bit of chili sauce.
Yes, sir.
Looks good.
Look at that!
Mushrooms and broccoli with basil marinade.
I love this kind of thing.
Put some sauce on it.
Yes, sir.
That's all I have.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Now, I've been thinking about how to serve it.
I'm not very good at it.
I am, you know.
I'm not even good at cooking buffet food.
What do you mean, "I'm not good at it"? Is there a fake theory?
I wish I couldn't come up with them all.
I wish I couldn't come up with all of them, but I can't get them all right.
I've laid it out here.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Bon appétit!
I'll start with the soup.
Yum!
Delicious!
It's so good to have hot food!
It's really good!
Yum!
Bon appétit!
What's this? Kazuto.
Kazuto.
It's an Indonesian bugbear.
It's an antelope.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
So soft!
What?
I want to use it for ramen.
It's good.
Takasaku, how does it taste?
Hmm? It's a Spanish omelet, right?
Oh-ho-ho!
This is my favorite.
It's all good, but so far...
Takasaku is so good!
Yum!
I'll have some eggplant, then.
It's pretty good.
I love soft eggplant.
It's delicious!
Here's a commercial!
Great!
Say "Yum!" once.
Let it echo through the Pacifico!
Say "Yum!" to the Pacifico.
I'll make the best sound I can.
That's good.
Oh, no.
Good.
Yum!
I'll have the mushrooms.
Oh!
What is this? What's this?
For now... the marina.
Yes, I'll have the marina.
That's what I'm talking about.
Wow, can you feel the ocean? Marie, can you feel it?
Yes, I can feel it. It's right next to the ocean.
The salt is gone, so it's good. It's very good.
It's great. The chopsticks are cracked.
I love it. I hate splitting chopsticks.
I just thought of that. That's great.
So, there was a soup spoon?
Yes, look at it.
No, thank you.
There it is! Oh, man! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
The seasoning is not too strong.
It tastes really good before a concert!
This is great! Reminds me of school lunch!
What's with the rice?
Put the rice on that side.Put the rice on that side.
No, I'm just afraid of eating too much rice.
Okay, eggplant, spinach and carrots.
It's all stuck together. I can't get any rice out.
Yes, it's good.
It's good!
Full of nutrients.
Have a good day.
I can't imagine what it's like at this point.
But the fact remains that I'm going to be there.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the audience in that big auditorium.
I'm looking forward to seeing all the audience and all the observers in that big space.
I hope to be able to share the best space with all the audience and all the observers.
I'll do my best to make the show the best it can be.
So I'm off to Rehasol!
Thank you very much!
Three, two, one.
Let me hear it.
Thank you very much for watching.
This is my Mr. Date.
This is Mr. Yoshi's Kanazashi. Pleased to meet you.
Hi!
You're like that high school boy.
Don't play with me, Mr. Joy.
Ugh!
Love with you, love with you, love with you, love with you, love with you
More, more, more.
Nietzsche.
The end.
Storm verein
presidency
So, rehearsal's over for the encore, and now it's time to get down to business.
Well, we've already done everything we can.
We're just going to do it, and then we're just going to have fun, and I know a lot of you have come from far away.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who are coming from far away, so even though it's cold, thank you very much.
So, that's it.
That's all for now.
Just the right amount of smear.
This guy, this guy, he blows fire. Over there. Beam.
That sure looks like a light.
This is totally different.
Not even close.
And so the rehearsal for the day was over.
Well, yes...
Pacifico is really big!
It was really big.
I'm so happy that we're going to perform here.
I'm very happy that we're going to perform here.
I think we have to make it a success here.
I'm sure we'll do our best here.
I want to do my very best
I want to give a great live performance.
I'll do my best!
Kanta, sing cheerfully!
Sing, sing, sing!
Let's have fun today.
It's only once, so let's go for it!
Okay, okay...
Heh heh heh heh heh heh
You should drive.
Right
Into a whirlpool of ouchy, ouchy, ouchy ickles.
You can't have a life, you've made up your mind.
Joint to the world
A-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
Here I swing
With courage
I'll be messing around
This body
If it has to be
I don't know
I don't have a choice
now is the time
I'll get caught up in the blame
if you do it again and again
I'll get the blame.
If you repeat it, you'll get it
If you could just say
If you can just say it
Somehow
How often
Power and strength
Straightforward
Very
Blue
Only those who are
can feel it
I'm near
is far away
is
The name
deliver it to me
important
to someone
I can tell.
Can you?
Beyond the connection
Every second a memory
As the evening rises
Until it blows up in the air
It feels like this.
I can hear it, can't I?
Now, that's why I'm going to finish up
Let's go see everyone's face
No, Fukazawa!
Fukazawa, let's go!
Sakuma, let's go!
Mukai, whoo!
Fukazawa, let's go!
Mukai, I'm counting, kun.
Mukai, swing away when we run.
Abe, thanks!
Mukai, thank you!
Abe, Sakuma-kun, on my count!
Abe, staff member!
Abe, staff member. Abe, staff member. Thank you!
Mukai Thank you, Iwamoto-san!
Thank you so much for today!
It's been a very exciting few months for me.
I'm really glad that this day ended happily and happily.
I'm really glad that it ended happily and happily!
I'm looking forward to the next day when we can all work together again.
Thank you so much for today!
Bye bye, I was so happy!
Thank you very much for the Yokohama concert, Kazuhiko!
Well, it was really a dream stage for us.
I'm so happy to be able to perform in Yokohama, which is one of our dream stage.
I thought we've done it so well!
I think we could not have performed any better than this.
I think we were able to show them a live performance that they will never be able to do any more.
However, there are still many things that we need to work on.
I think there are still a lot of things missing.
I think there are still a lot of things we need to work on.
I hope you will practice a lot and grow up.
I would like to practice a lot and grow up.
The next concert will be a hall tour.
Please look forward to it!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much for your performance in Yokohama.
Thank you very much.
Well, I really wonder what the cause is.
The cause is in me, and this time I'm going to do the set.
We have been working as if this cause was our own until now.
The history of all 7 of us working together
I feel again that it was a live performance that made me look back on the history of our activities.
I feel it again.
From the very first song, I felt like I was going to cry.
I felt like I was about to cry.
I felt like I was going to cry from the very first song.When I thought that this observer was so supportive of us
When I thought that this observer was so supportive of us
I started to cry.
I was so moved
It was a mixture of nervousness and emotion.
I was so nervous and moved by this song.
I was so nervous and moved by the song.
through the song, and as we created a space together
As we created a space together
I was having more and more fun.
I think the observers and the seven of us
I think the seven of us and the observers were able to see a wonderful view.
It was such a great live performance.
I feel again that it was such a great concert.
We are not satisfied with Pacifica Yokohama yet.
We seven of us think that this is just a passing point.
More and more months are coming up.
Next is the hall tour in July and August.
It may still be a high wall for us.
but we will keep working hard to achieve this goal.
We will do our best to achieve this goal.
I hope we can achieve this goal.
If you would like to join us
I look forward to your continued support.
This is Taku Ogura.
Thank you very much.
Real Space Case 5 End of Infinity has ended successfully!
Thank you very much!
The Pacifico Yokohama's National Grand Hall was really big!
It was the first time for me to be there.
But...
Everyone really enjoyed the show.
I thought to myself as I sang that they had come to see us after listening to our 3rd album "Infinite There".
I was thinking as I sang that they had come to the concert after listening to our 3rd album "Infinite There".
Thank you so much!
I'm glad you're enjoying every bit of Infinite Myself.
I'm glad to know that you are enjoying every bit of it.
Well, for me, it was in Yokohama, so...
It was about a year ago that the seven of us performed in Yokohama.
We had a chance to talk together in Yamashita Park about 2 or 3 years ago.
I remember that too.
I don't know...
Yes, that's right.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yokohama, Hashimoto Yokohama, I will never forget what happened today. From now on.
Thank you very much for the local no-space case 5.
Let's continue to run through with the seven of us and the observers that we have on site.
Thank you. Thank you for today.